A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 5, Accession 2017:061 FA1472
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 5, Accession 2017:061
1969-2007
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation
FA1472
36.52 Cubic Feet 83 letter-sized document boxes
Biographical / Historical
The Henry Luce Foundation was established by Henry R. Luce in 1936. As a New York-based nonprofit organization, the Luce Foundation awards grants in American Art, Asian studies, Higher Education, Theology, and supports the Clare Boothe Luce Program for women in science, mathematics, and engineering.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the Henry Luce Foundation in 2017.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
All inquiries to view films require advanced notice of at least 2 business days, and may necessitate notice of up to one week. Individual items, including those that are not available in modern formats, may be restricted from access at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
The Henry Luce Foundation records (Record Group 5) consists primarily of grant and professorship files.
Arrangement
The Henry Luce Foundation records (Record Group 5) are arranged as follows:
Series 1: Project Files, 1988-2007
Series 2: Professorship Files, 1969-2001
Related Materials
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 1, Accession 2017:057 (FA1317)
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 2, Accession 2017:058 (FA1393)
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 3, Accession 2017:059 (FA1410)
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 4, Accession 2017:060 (FA1442)
Art, American; Research grants -- Asia, Southeastern; Education, Higher; Theology -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; United States -- Relations -- China
- Project Files, 1988-2007; 1
  - Carnegie Museum of Art - Merchant Prince and Master Builder: Edgar Kaufmann and Frank Lloyd Wright, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Case Western University, Mandel Center for Nonprofit Organizations - Arts Management Program, 1992-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Center for the Arts, Religion and Education - Publish the Illustrations in "The Religious Art of Andy Warhol", 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Center for the Arts, Religion and Education - Publish the Illustrations in "Visual Theology: Images in the 16th Century Reformation", 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Center for Creative Photography (University of Arizona) - Collection Awareness Program (American Collection Enhancement (ACE) Initiative), 1998-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Center for Immigration Studies - Research Fellowships in Immigration Policy Studies, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Center for Marine Conservation - Shark Conservation and "Fish for the Future", 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Center for National Policy - Support a Conference Examining Model Programs which Prevent Youth Violence, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Center for the Study of the Presidency - Fellowships, Scholarships, 25th Annual Student Symposium, and Leadership Conferences, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
  - Center for Theology and Land (Wartburg Theological Seminary) - Revisioning Rural Ministry, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Center of Theological Inquiry - Publish the Illustrations in "Calvinism and Visual Arts", 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Center on Congress (Indiana University) - Interactive Internet Program, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Central Park Conservancy - Ascent Program, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Central Park Conservancy - Henry Luce Nature Observatory, 1993-1999 (Box 3, Folder 16-18)
    - Belvedere Castle, Henry Luce Observatory, 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box T1)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Centurion Ministries, Inc. - Program for Falsely Convicted Individuals in Prison, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Ceres - Miriam Milgram Presentation at the Second International Textile Symposium, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Cheekwood Museum of Art - Art of William Edmondson, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Chicago Panel on School Policy - Fellowships in Educational Policy, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 22-23)
  - Children's Aid Society - Leadership Development Programs, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 24-25)
  - China Institute in America - "Abstraction and Expression" Chinese Calligraphy Exhibit, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - China Institute in America - Increase Understanding of Chinese Art, Culture, and Society, 1996-1999 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Chinese Language Teachers Association, Inc. - Leadership Seminar Project, 1994-2000 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Chinese People's Association for Friendship with Foreign Countries - Museum, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Chinese People's Association for Friendship with Foreign Countries - Staff Training Program #2, 1995-2007 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong - Christian Colleges in China Archives, 1995-2001 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks - Computers and Software in the New Boston Office, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks - Warren Ost Memorial Fund, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Church of St. Emeric - Father Luis Dolan Retirement Fund, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Church World Service - Meeting on No Gun Ri Korean War Incident, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Citizen's Committee for New York City - Neighborhood Leadership Institute, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 36-37)
  - Citizen's Committee for New York City - Young Citizen Center Program in the International High School, 2001-2005 (Box 6, Folder 38-39)
  - City Innovation - Executives in Schools Program, 1990-1999 (Box 6, Folder 40-41)
  - City University of New York - "Perspectives on Modern Art: Identity, Institutions, and Images" Symposium, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Cityscape Institute - Public Space Improvement, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Classroom, Inc. - Assessment Study of Computer Simulations on Learning (Student Outcomes of an Instructional Innovation: Classroom Inc.'s Longitudinal Study 2000-2003), 1999-2004 (Box 7, Folder 44-45)
  - Classroom, Inc. - Professional Development Program, 1993-1998 (Box 7, Folder 46-47)
  - Cleveland Scholarship Programs, Inc. - Early Intervention Advisory Services Program for High School Students, 1996-2003 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Coalition of Essential Schools (Brown University) - National Re:Learning Faculty, 1992-2001 (Box 8, Folder 49-50)
  - College of Wooster - Henry Jefferson Copeland Campus Minister, 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Columbia Theological Seminary - Romans: Together for Good, 2000-2003 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Columbia University - Alternative Medicine Course at New York Botanical Garden, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Columbia University - Constitutionalism and Human Rights in China, 1991-1999 (Box 9, Folder 54-55)
  - Columbia University - Korean War Documents Project, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Columbia University - Sustainable Development Initiative, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Columbia University, Center for United States-China Exchange - Chinese Designers and Planners, 1994-1999 (Box 9, Folder 58-59)
  - Columbia University, College of Physicians and Surgeons - Continuing Education in Botanical Medicine, 1997-2001 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Columbia University, East Asian Institute - Southeast Asia in World Affairs Seminar, 1998-2002 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Columbia University, East Asian Institute - United States-Japan Collaboration on Southeast Asian Human Rights, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Columbia University, Teachers College - Center on Chinese Education, 2000-2005 (Box 10, Folder 63-64)
  - Columbus Museum - Southeast Art Museum Consortium's Collaborative Exhibit Program (American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative, 1999-2006 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Community for Education Foundation - Overcoming Obstacles Program, 1999-2003 (Box 10, Folder 66-67)
  - Community Preparatory School - Scholarships for At-Risk Youth, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Connecticut College - Planning Grant, 2000-2002 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Connecticut College - Renovation of Dana Hall (Renamed for Jack Evans), 1998 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Connecticut Historical Society - "Connecticut Valley Furniture: Eliphalet Chapin and His Contemporaries, 1750-1850" Exhibition and Catalog, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Connecticut Historical Society - Signboard Collection, 1998-2001 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Conservation International - Climate and Biodiversity: Modeling for Change, 2001-2004 (Box 12, Folder 73-74)
  - Constitutional Education Foundation, Inc. - Constitution Workers: An Afterschool Legal Education and Mentoring Program for New York City High School Students, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 75-76)
  - Cooper Hewitt National Design Museum - American Prints and Drawing Center, 1995-1999 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Cooper Hewitt National Design Museum - Henry Luce Study Room for American Art, 1999-2002 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art - National Art Museum for Children, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art - New Paintings Storage System, 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Cornell College - Construction and Endowment of a New Art Gallery in Honor of Peter Paul Luce, 1998-2012 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Cornell University Library - Preservation and Conservation Internship, 1996-2001 (Box 13, Folder 82-83)
  - Council for a Community of Democracies - Warsaw Process, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Council for a Community of Democracies - Second International Conference, Korea, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Council for a Parliament of the World's Religions - Symposium in Capetown, South Africa, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Council for Spiritual and Ethical Education - Religious Literacy, 1998-2001 (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - Council on Foreign Relations - Shipping Back Issues of "Foreign Affairs" Journal to the Institute of United States and Canada Studies in Moscow, 1996-1999 (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - Council on Library and Information Resources - Southeast Asian Libraries and Archives, 2001-2004 (Box 14, Folder 89)
  - Crossroads (Evangelicals for Social Action) - Holistic Churches Development, 1994-1999 (Box 14, Folder 90)
  - Currier Gallery of Art - "Impressionism Reformed: Paintings of Edmund C. Tarbell" Exhibition and Catalog, 1997-2002 (Box 14, Folder 91)
  - Currier Gallery of Art - Research and Computerization of Collections (American Collections Enhancements (ACE) Initiative), 2000-2005 (Box 15, Folder 92)
  - Dallas Museum of Art - "That Earlier, Wilder Image: Oil Sketches by American Landscape Painters, 1830-1880" Exhibition and Catalog, 1996-1999 (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - Delaware Art Museum - John Sloan Art Collection Research Project (American Art Exchange (ACE) Initiative), 1998-2003 (Box 15, Folder 94)
  - Delta Ministries - Assistant Director Position, 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - Des Moines Art Center - Resource Preservation and Dissemination (American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative), 1999-2003 (Box 15, Folder 96)
  - Desert Community College District - Landscaping of Main Entrance, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 97)
  - Dickinson College - Diaspora and Community Studies, 1999-2005 (Box 15, Folder 98)
  - The Dome Project, Inc. - Juvenile Justice Program, 1995-1998 (Box 16, Folder 99)
  - The Door - Clemente Course in the Humanities, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 100)
    Scope and Contents
    Courses in humanities for at-risk youth.
  - Doubleday Babcock Senior Center - New Building Costs, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 101)
  - The Drawing Center - "Heavenly Visions: Shaker Gift Drawings and Gift Songs" Exhibition and Catalog, 1999-2002 (Box 16, Folder 102-103)
  - Duke University - Religion and Arts Planning Grant, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 104)
  - East Side House Settlement - Family Literacy Program, 1996-1998 (Box 16, Folder 105)
  - East-West Center - Archaeology Training for Cambodian Students, 1995-2005 (Box 17, Folder 106)
  - EastBridge - Asian Studies Publishing Venture, 2001-2004 (Box 17, Folder 107)
  - Eastern Baptist Theological Seminary - Continuing Education Program, 1999-2002 (Box 17, Folder 108)
  - Eastern Baptist Theological Seminary - Doctor of Ministry Program, 1994-1999 (Box 17, Folder 109)
  - Eastern Cluster of Lutheran Seminaries - Integrated Library System, 2000-2005 (Box 17, Folder 110)
  - George Eastman House International Museum of Photography and Film - "Young America: The Daguerreotypes of Southworth and Hawes" Exhibition and Catalog, 2001-2006 (Box 18, Folder 111-112)
  - Educational Resources and Referrals (China) - Religious Studies Department and Conference, Peking University, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 113)
  - Eden Theological Seminary - James Good Collection Cataloger, 1996-2000 (Box 18, Folder 114)
  - Eisenhower Exchange Fellowships - Fellows from China, 1998-2000 (Box 18, Folder 115)
  - Emory University, Rollins School of Public Health - Interfaith Health Program, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 116)
  - Enterprise Foundation in New York City - Neighborhood Planning Initiative, 1995-1998 (Box 19, Folder 117)
  - Episcopal Church Foundation - Canterbury Cathedral's Education for the Ages, 1997-2001 (Box 19, Folder 118)
  - Farnsworth Art Museum - 50th Anniversary Collection Celebration (American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative), 1997-2001 (Box 19, Folder 119-120)
  - Fashion Institute of Technology - China Chic: East Meets West, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 121)
  - Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR) - Moratorium Promotion and Education, 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 122)
  - Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR) - Public Information and Education, 1997-1999 (Box 19, Folder 123)
  - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies - Church Desk Program, 1995-2002 (Box 19, Folder 124)
  - Fellowship Academy, Inc. - Tuition for Inner-City Children, 1998-2003 (Box 20, Folder 125)
  - Henry L. Ferguson Museum - Expansion and Renewal, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 126)
  - Fifth Avenue Presbyterian Church - Kirkland Scholar in Residence Program, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 127)
  - First Congregational Church - Refugee Assistance, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 128)
  - First Presbyterian Church in the City of New York - Center for the Arts and the Church, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 129)
  - First Presbyterian Church of Oyster - Ralph and Betty Lewis Scholarship, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 130)
  - Fisher's Island Library Association - Building Renovation, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 131)
  - Fiorentino Foundation - Sign Language Program, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 132)
  - Foreign Policy Association - Great Decisions National Opinion Ballot, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 133)
  - Foreign Policy Association - Great Decisions Public TV Series, 2000-2003 (Box 20, Folder 134)
  - Foreign Policy Association - Great Decisions on Campus Program, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 135)
  - Foreign Policy Association - Great Decisions on Campus Program, 2001-2005 (Box 20, Folder 136)
  - Foundation for Teaching Economics - Economy and the Environment, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 137)
  - Foundation for Teaching Economics - The Environment and the Economy Teachers' Training Program, 2000-2002 (Box 21, Folder 138-140)
  - Foundation for Teaching Economics - Minority Participation in Economics for Leaders Program, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 141)
  - Fourth Presbyterian Church of Chicago - Fund Expenses of "When True Simplicity is Gained" by Martin and Micah Marty, 1996-1998 (Box 21, Folder 142)
  - Fowler Museum of Cultural History, University of California, Los Angeles - "The Art of Rice: Spirit of Sustenance in Asia" Exhibition and Catalog, 2000-2004 (Box 21, Folder 143-144)
  - Franciscan Friars of the Atonement - Collections on the Internet, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 145)
  - Franklin Pierce College - Francis X. Cheney Lectureship in Religion and Society, 1997-2002 (Box 22, Folder 146)
  - Franklin Pierce College - Making Sense of Place Program, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 147)
  - Freer Art Gallery and Arthur Sackler Gallery - Center for the Conservation of Chinese Paintings, 2000-2005 (Box 22, Folder 148)
  - Freer Art Gallery and Arthur Sackler Gallery - Imperial Art Collection from Japan, 1997-2000 (Box 22, Folder 149)
  - Fresh Air Fund - Fast Track Project, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 150)
  - Frick Collection - Fellows Program, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 151)
  - Frick Collection - Henry Clay Frick Fellow, 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 152)
  - Friends of Olana, Inc. - Restoration of Frederic Church's Home, 1996-2001 (Box 22, Folder 153-154)
  - Friends of the Family Academy - Music Program, 1998-2003 (Box 23, Folder 155)
  - Friends of Gloucester Council on Aging - Rose Baker Senior Center, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 156)
  - Fuller Theological Seminary - Consultation on Global Church History, 1997-2004 (Box 23, Folder 157)
  - Fundacion Amistad - Environmental Education in Cuba, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 158)
  - Fund for Theological Education - Ministerial Candidates for Theological Education, 1998-2002 (Box 23, Folder 159-161, Box 24, Folder 162-163)
  - Garden Conservancy - Documentary Film on Conservation Efforts, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 164)
  - Garden Conservancy - Humes Japanese Stroll Gardens, 1997-1999 (Box 24, Folder 165)
  - Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum - John Singer Sargent: The Late Landscapes, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 166)
  - Gay Men's Health Crisis, Inc. - AIDS, Children, and Families, 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 167)
  - General Theological Seminary of the Episcopal Church - Center for Christian Spirituality, 2001-2005 (Box 24, Folder 168)
  - George Washington University - Southeast Asia Historian, 1996-2001 (Box 25, Folder 169)
  - George Washington University - Surveying China, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 170)
  - Germantown Mennonite Historic Trust - Anabaptist-Mennonite Architecture Conference, 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 171)
  - Gilcrease Museum - Collection Awareness Initiative, "Thomas Moran" (American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative), 1997-2001 (Box 25, Folder 172)
  - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York, Inc. - Senior Girl Scout College Prep Program, 2001-2005 (Box 25, Folder 173)
  - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York, Inc. - World Discovery Program, 1998-2000 (Box 25, Folder 174)
  - Global Forum of Spiritual and Parliamentary Leaders on Human Survival - Matching Grant, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 175)
  - Global Forum of Spiritual and Parliamentary Leaders on Human Survival - Planning Future Fora, 1996-1999 (Box 26, Folder 176)
  - Global Forum of Spiritual and Parliamentary Leaders on Human Survival - World Assembly for Reconciliation, 1995-2002 (Box 26, Folder 177)
  - Global Kids - International College and Career Exploration Program, 2000-2003 (Box 26, Folder 178)
  - Gomez Foundation for Mill House - Restoration of the Mill, 1996-1999 (Box 26, Folder 179)
  - Good Shepherd Services - Program for Promising Student Dropouts, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 180)
  - Goodwill Industries of Greater New York - Cops and Kids Program for Youth at Risk, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 181)
  - Edwin Gould Academy - Positive Peer Culture Program, 1995-2000 (Box 27, Folder 182)
  - The Graduate Center - "American Art at the Crossroads" Symposium, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 183)
  - Martha Graham Center of Contemporary Dance - Training Scholarship Program, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 184)
  - Florence Griswold Museum - Installation, Study Center, and Storage for American Art Collection, 2001-2003 (Box 27, Folder 185-186)
  - Haleakala, Inc. (The Kitchen) - Video Archive Project, 2001-2004 (Box 27, Folder 187)
  - Harlem Center for Education - Summer High School Academic Program, 1997-2000 (Box 27, Folder 188)
  - Harlem Educational Activities Fund (HEAF) - High Expectations Program, 1999-2002 (Box 27, Folder 189-190)
  - Harlem Educational Activities Fund (HEAF) - Mentoring Program, 1996-2001 (Box 28, Folder 191-192)
  - Harlem School of the Arts, Inc. - Capital Campaign, 1992-1994 (Box 28, Folder 193)
  - Hartwick College - International Curriculum Development and Study Abroad, 1995-2002 (Box 28, Folder 194-195)
  - Harvard University - Modern Chinese Historiography, 1995-1999 (Box 28, Folder 196)
  - Harvard University Art Museums (Fogg Art Museum) - American Art Visiting Scholars, 1992-2001 (Box 28, Folder 197)
  - Harvard University, Asia Center - Religion, Economics, and Politics in Contemporary Asia, 1997-2003 (Box 29, Folder 198)
  - Harvard University, Divinity School - Urban Ministry Program (Renewal), 2000-2003 (Box 29, Folder 199)
  - Harvard University, John King Fairbank Center for East Asian Research - Chinese "Holocaust" Project, 1990-1998 (Box 29, Folder 200)
  - Harvard University, John King Fairbank Center for East Asian Research - Mao's Road to Power, 1996-1998 (Box 29, Folder 201)
  - Harvard University, Law School - Preserve Newly Discovered Chinese Legal Texts, 1998-2003 (Box 29, Folder 202)
  - Healthcare Chaplaincy - Center for Pastoral Education, 1996-2001 (Box 29, Folder 203)
  - Healthcare Chaplaincy - Pastoral Research Department and Library, 2001-2012 (Box 30, Folder 204-205)
  - Heckscher Museum of Art, 1993-1999 (Box 30, Folder 206)
  - Henry Art Gallery - American Art Initiative (American Collections Enhancement (ACE) Initiative), 1997-2001 (Box 30, Folder 207)
  - Henry Street Settlement - Expanded Horizons Program for At-Risk Youth, 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 208)
  - High Museum of Art - "After Whistler: The Artist and His Influence on American Painting" Exhibition and Catalog, 2000-2004 (Box 30, Folder 209)
  - High Museum of Art - John Henry Twachtman Exhibition and Catalog, 1997-2000 (Box 31, Folder 210)
  - Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden - Edward Ruscha Exhibit, 1998-2000 (Box 31, Folder 211)
  - Hollins University - Leadership Program, 1992-1998 (Box 31, Folder 212)
  - Hong Kong-American Center, Chinese University of Hong Kong - Philanthropy Study, 1995-1998 (Box 31, Folder 213)
  - Honolulu Academy of Arts - Henry R. Luce Wing and Luce Pavilion, 1999-2003 (Box 31, Folder 214-215)
  - Hood Museum of Art, Dartmouth College - American Drawings and Watercolors (ACE), 1997-2005 (Box 32, Folder 216-217)
  - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution, and Peace - Political Pluralisms in Taiwan, 1992-1998 (Box 32, Folder 218)
  - Horace Mann School - Summer on the Hill Program, 1997-1999 (Box 32, Folder 219)
  - Horace Mann School - Summer on the Hill Program (Renewal), 2001-2006 (Box 32, Folder 220)
  - Horticulture Society of New York - New Technology at HSNY's Library, 1995-1997 (Box 32, Folder 221)
  - Hudson River Museum of Westchester - "Hanging by a Thread" Exhibition and Catalog, 1997-2000 (Box 32, Folder 222)
  - Huguenot Heritage - Huguenot Cultural History, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 223)
  - Human Rights Watch - Religion and Human Rights in Asia, 1996-2001 (Box 33, Folder 224)
  - Hunter Museum of Art - Catalog and Promote Awareness of Collections, 1997-2002 (Box 33, Folder 225)
  - Huntington Library, Art Collections, and Botanical Gardens - "Nexus of Exchange" Exhibition and Catalog, 1999-2002 (Box 33, Folder 226-227)